[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Your wife?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I got a little emotional.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "When you hear those words, what do you think?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I feel fine.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "How are you feeling now?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "You know, I think my mom and dad took the news far worse than I did.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "I mean how have your mom and dad been?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "They're -- you know, they're very supportive.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Your sisters?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I guess the most prominent symptom was my legs went numb for two months, something like that.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "What kind of things?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Yes, it's usually at night when I'm injecting myself with a giant needle full of, you know, full of stuff that's supposed to, you know, keep me out a wheel chair.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Do you still have moments, though, when you look in the mirror any morning you think why me, why now?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I believe the title when I was involved was \"Stars on Stripes.\"", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "What was the show?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "It was a -- kind of a military-style show, action/adventure, things like that.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "And you would have been doing what?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "It was -- well, I was never told.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "And the only reason was because they couldn't insure you or what was the reason?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "To a degree.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Do you fear that others may follow suit?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Yes, Piers, thanks for having me.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "And what kind of life can Jack now expect, given he's 26 years old?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "You know, I think my biggest -- you know, from what I've been researching is, you know, stem cell research.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Endless people telling you?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Yes -- yes.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Sanjay?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, we're still trying to sort through it all.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Benjamin Crump, what is your reaction to all the tape material that's come out today?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's the crux of the matter, Piers.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "So in terms of that significance to how much we should believe in what George Zimmerman says in totality, how important is that, do you think?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Has that person come forward, made any statements?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, the judge said last week that the information was going to come out.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "What is the purpose of putting this all out now?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, the concern I have, Piers, is that I truly am not at liberty to do an analysis of the evidence.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "As we've discussed, his credibility was certainly affected by the fact that he stood mute when his wife said something that turned out to be a misrepresentation to the court about the funds.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "How much of a problem is it that his credibility is now being damaged?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "That witness has made a statement.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "The witness that George Zimmerman describes in the video today from the property directly adjoining where this incident finally took place, do you know if that witness has come forward and made a statement that corroborates what George is saying?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, multifaceted.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "How would you describe his mood?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Piers, I was just going to use the same term you used.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What was your reaction and your client's reaction to that bombshell, as it turned out to be?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Well, I've been in the courtroom every day, from the opening statements until the end of the closing arguments and the jury charge.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "How do you feel the trial has gone in term of your client's interest and those of the other young people who came forward, who claimed they've been abused as children?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, the Jerry Sandusky that I knew and have come to know over the past 28 years spent his life trying to help kids overcome their circumstances.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Why are you so convinced, given the mountain of evidence to the contrary, that he is innocent of ever abusing a child?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I certainly wouldn't now.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "I mean, would you ever have naked showers with boys of 12, 13, 14?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I really have no idea.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Do you feel that he's going to be acquitted?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I don't think there's anything wrong with those behaviors.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Did you ever see anything that you thought was a little odd?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Yeah, I knew Matt fairly well.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Did you know Matt Sandusky, his adopted son?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I'm not all that shocked by a kid who at the beginning of the trial is for him, at the end of the trial is against him.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "So are you as shocked as everybody else that he now is making it clear that he was abused by Jerry Sandusky, or claims to have been?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't understand -- I don't claim to understand the rationale behind the attorney's actions.", "docId": "120621pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "If Jerry Sandusky is as innocent as you think he is, why did this defense put up this strange claim that he suffered from this syndrome called Histrionic Personality Disorder?", "qSentId": 574}]